Roll the mouse wheel back and forth to search for the map in the 3D window.
Press the mouse button and move the mouse to scale.
The scale will maintain the original map search and angle.
Press the mouse button and move the mouse to rotate to check the details.
Press the button in the 3D window to rotate and adjust the engagement position.
The function is called focus.
Press the mouse button and move the mouse to the preview view in the menu.
Or press the number button to change the view.
Press the mouse button and move the mouse to change the view.
Similarly, in the 2D window, rotate the mouse wheel to zoom in and out.
The difference is that the 2D window will be zoomed in and out with the mouse pointer as the center.
The center of the mouse and the movement of the mouse can be parallel.
In addition, you can change the speed control settings in the user settings.
It is up to you to choose other 3D software settings or change specific settings.